Ankit Mishra

Sr. UX/UI Designer

28 Years, BMM Degree Mumbai (India)

SKILLS SET

User Journey

User Flow

UX Research

UX Audit

CRO Audit

User Interface Design

Wireframing

Information Architecture

Prototyping

Interactive Design

Photography

Cinematography

Video Editing

TOOLS

Figma

Sketch

Adobe XD

Adobe Photoshop

Adobe Premiere Pro

Adobe After Effects

Adobe Invision

Google Analytics

Hotjar

Invision

Zeplin

OTHER SKILLS

Cinemagraph

Print Design

CONTACT DETAILS

Email: ankitm616@gmail.com

Contact: +91 902-992-7190

PORTFOLIO LINKS

Dribbble: https://dribbble.com/ankitmishra

PROFILE

I have 5.8+ years of experience in creating UX/UI solutions for complex web and mobile interfaces, expertized in understanding business goals, User Research, design thinking, wireframing, UX interactive prototyping, final UI graphics production.

I've had the pleasure to work with clients such as Adidas, Red bull, The Economists, Eurofinance and Zee Educare and GBF.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Sr. UI/UX Designer, Axioned

Jul 2019 - Present - Thane, Mumbai

- · Review of business and user objectives
- Create Information architecture and User Journey
- Help visualize, communicate, and implement designs and assets
- Perform User Experience audit for retainer client's
- Research best practises with effective solutions
- Lead design initiative in revamping the web & mobile application.
- Collaborate with cross-functional teams like product managers, developers, designers and QA team
- Illustrate design ideas, process flows and sitemaps
- Gather data through the GA and Hotjar for UX
- Identify and troubleshoot UX problems
- Create UI mockups, prototypes and Interaction design
- Alter layout adjustments based on client's feedback
- Work on style standards like fonts, colors, and images
- Provide guidance for junior designers and interns
- Support with converstion and speed optimization

Ankit Mishra

Sr. UX/UI Designer

28 Years, BMM Degree Mumbai (India)

SKILLS SET

User Journey

User Flow

UX Research

UX Audit

CRO Audit

User Interface Design

Wireframing

Information Architecture

Prototyping

Interactive Design

Photography

Cinematography

Video Editing

TOOLS

Figma

Sketch

Adobe XD

Adobe Photoshop

Adobe Premiere Pro

Adobe After Effects

Adobe Invision

Google Analytics

Hotjar

Invision

Zeplin

OTHER SKILLS

Cinemagraph

Print Design

WORK EXPERIENCE

UI/UX Designer, Achieveee Design & Developement

Nov 2015 - Jul 2019 - Kalyan, Thane

- Gather and evaluate clients and users requirements.
- Illustrate design ideas, process flows and sitemaps.
- Create UI mockups and prototypes.
- Identify and troubleshoot UX problems.
- Alter layout adjustments based on client's feedback.
- Work on style standards like fonts, colors, and images.
- Lead design initiative in revamping the web application.
- Collabrate with developers for proper implementations.
- Cordinate with clients and reply to their emails.
- Attend calls directly from client's and understand their requirement

Graphic Designer, Peak Performance Pvt. Ltd.

Nov 2014 - Oct 2015 - Andheri, Mumbai

- Develop creative posts as per the requirement.
- Create Logo, Brochures, Standees, Manual Books and Emailers
- · Layout, typography, Colour and Icons
- Print banners design for conferences

EDUCATION

Bachelor in Mass Media

Birla College of Arts, Science & Commerce

2010- 2010, Kalyan

H.S.C

Saket College of Arts, Science & Commerce

2007 - 2009, Kalyan